jobthread.com 2016-05-29

# JobThread | Privacy Policy

The simple version 

We have a simple policy: We'll never sell, rent or give away your personal information to anyone. 

Questions or Comments 

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.jobthread.com/contact?ref=privacy). 

Privacy Policy (the full version) 

Introduction 

JobThread, Inc. respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at JobThread, Inc.'s Web site. 

Part I. Information Collection 

JobThread, Inc. collects personally identifiable information through our "Sign Up" page as well as various other pages throughout the site. We collect the following information about primary visitors when new users create an account via our "Sign Up" page: Email address, First Name, Last Name, Zip code. 

We collect demographic data in order to understand where our product is being used. 

We employ cookies on our site. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable JobThread, Inc. to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. 

JobThread, Inc. does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. 

Part II. Information Usage. 

The information collected by JobThread, Inc. will be used to help ensure the security of users data. Users who provide information will be able to log in, logout, create JobThread postings, pass on JobThread postings to others and Apply to a JobThread posting that they have received. 

We do not share personally identifiable data with any third parties except when authorized by you and needed to complete your request. 

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. 

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy without notice. 

Part III. Access to Information 

Users may access their own personal information via their "Settings" page and contact us about inaccuracies they may find. Users may change their personal information via their "Settings" page. 

Part IV. Problem Resolution 

If problems arise, users may contact JobThread, Inc. via our [Contact Us](http://www.jobthread.com/contact?ref=privacy) page. 

Part V. Data Storage and Security 

JobThread, Inc. protects user information with a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. 

Questions or Comments 

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.jobthread.com/contact?ref=privacy).
